Hey, what's up everybody? Listen, we all
know that trying to have unique videos
and stuff for our ads is sometimes a
challenge. What actually resonates with
people? There's different styles of ads
now that have been running really well
that have been connecting with people
lately using Instagram ads, having video
that's running with then some text over
it. And I'm going to show you an example
of what I mean by that exactly. And I'm
going to show you how I was able to
actually create something like this as
well using AI. Those are the style of of
ads and ad creatives that are working
really well. So today I actually went to
work and I'm and I'm going to break down
my whole process of how I did this
today. I went to work and I created this
video right here. Okay, so this is an AI
generated video that I thought was
really cool. Number one, how did I come
up with this concept? I actually looked
at a lot of my different competitors
that were out there, the types of offers
that they had around a similar niche.
They all seem to be running ads
something related to a beach or
something like that. I'm like, "Okay,
great." So, I reverse engineered. This
is the first step, and this is something
I want you to like write down and pay
attention to. Let me see if I can put
this put this on the on the whiteboard
here. Number
one, you want to look at competitor
analysis. Okay?
And this is very important when it comes
to your marketing and
advertising. I know that you want to be
original and and and you are an
original, but there are people that are
out there that have that are spending
money on ads and marketing in your niche
or have a similar related product or a
lead
magnet and they're testing ads. And
there's a reason why they're using
certain types of creatives because it
works. And so instead of trying to
reinvent the wheel, give your own spin
on it. So I found like five of my
competitors. They were all talking about
evergreen offers and things like that
because that's what my latest lead
magnet is about. But all the ads that
were working really well for them were
on a beach. It was either them on a
beach, a video of a beach, or a photo of
a beach, or them sitting on a boat
somewhere. And then it had the text over
it. So, I was like, "Okay, I'm going to
use AI to actually make me a couple
variations of a beach video." Got a
little this little like flamingo float
here. Such a great like attention
grabbing thing. I saw one of my
competitors had a great ad where he had
his face and name on it. I thought that
was really cool because it created that
connection factor. Even though it wasn't
him talking, it created that connection
factor by doing that. And then the text,
this is our threeline uh text right
here. Was able to actually generate this
using AI, using some of the prompts that
we've actually been able to come up
with. We have some different prompts
that we've been using lately
um for creating different types of
Instagram ads. Outcome, value
proposition, call to action style.
That's what this was. So, it's all about
the outcome, a bold statement on the
outcome, what is the value proposition,
and then the call to action. So you'll
notice outcome you're banking 30K a
month stress free in your coaching biz
my AI powered system. This is the value
proposition. This is the call to action
right there. So those three steps of
text on top of some kind of an animated
video. It's working really well. And you
can either record these videos yourself
uh or you can generate them or you can
go source them or find them somewhere
like from Art List or things like that.
I'm going to show you as well just like
a couple examples of these types of
video ads that I mean they're working
really well. Here's another another type
right here that I ran. This one was
working really well right there. It's me
dancing around
excited outcomebased value proposition.
Actually, this one's a little bit
different. This one is this one outcome.
Yeah, it's a it's a bold
question intrigue builder and then a
call to action. So, it's a little bit
different. And the prompt that that's a
two-step prompt. You can either try one
or two of these. What I like to do is
filter my landing page through these
prompts. And by the way, if you want
these prompts, you can go find them over
at my website. I have them always
available on my site. Free AI prompts
right here at the top of my website,
jermagowski.com. It's right here. Free
AI
prompts. Okay, there's the
props for/hatg. These are Chad GBT
prompts that have made our clients eight
figures, which is incredible and true.
Download the prompts, Google Doc. It's
Google Doc right
here. And and there's like sales copy,
landing pages, all this types of stuff
on here, which is awesome. Super cool.
These prompts like have helped. I use
them. These are all the ones I use in my
business and the ones that my clients
use. Under advertising though, this
Instagram ad prompt is one that's a
brand new one we just generated. And we
we actually used AI to help us write the
prompt. We reverse engineered a lot of
our best ads into it and it created
this. And so that's really cool is how
we were able to do that. All right, back
to what we were saying. So you can
either record a video of yourself like I
got going on right
here. This one did really well for us.
You can This one did good, too.
you
can generate the video or you can buy a
video and then you have text over it in
that style. So, I'm going to show you
how to use AI to kind of generate all of
these different types of things. So, for
one, we have our our like our offer and
what are we actually offering people?
This is this landing page right here.
This is a lead
magnet where we're directing people.
jeremicowsky.comevergreen. This is our
brand
new free class right here. You know, we
just had our free Instagram ads class
right
here. And these are, by the way, these
are lead magnets. These are what
generate leads to our email list. So,
what I do is I
teach a lesson that's just like really
incredible, a mini class right there,
give it away for free in exchange people
giving me their name and email address.
That's exactly what this is as well.
Same thing. Same type of thing. Okay. So
then I copy the sales
copy and then I can go into my AI and
use that prompt. So we'll go into chat
GBT right here. By the way, there's so
many different like versions now in chat
GBT. We got 40, we got 4.5, 03,
04. My goodness, my friends. Let's use
04 mini because it's actually this brand
new version that's really, really smart.
at
reasoning. Oh, for many high. So, I'm
going to go like this right here. I'm
going to go I want to generate some text
for Instagram video ads. Here's my sales
letter, please. And I'm going to take
the prompt. I'm going to put sales
letter in brackets. So this is a this is
a if you reference something like here's
my
this if you take bracket bracket you put
the two brackets like this and whatever
you referenced up here. So here's my dot
dot dot and then I have the same thing
named inside of brackets. I'm going to
paste it in there. It will recognize
that what'sever in between the brackets
is what I
referenced. And that's a great way to
help chat GPT not get lost in what
you're telling it to do. It's a best
practice with AI. Okay. So then I'm
going to copy this prompt right
here for what I want it to
do. So it's going to generate me some
different Instagram ads uh text right
here. Ready to scale your business. Not
burning out. Okay. So
again, not as punchy as I want. That's
why I said down here, you may want to
prompt the output to shorten and make
these more punchy. We found that for
some reason you got to do like a second
step and tell it shorten these and make
them more punchy and then it makes them
so much better. All right, there we go.
See, now it's just three lines just like
the the ads that I was showing you. Real
punchy. Scale this. Get my evergreen
system. Comment success. Stop hustling.
Start scaling. Ditch burnout. Hit 10 to
30k a month. watch my free class on
schedule with these. This is just great
for putting in these these video ads.
That that type of prompting was able to
then convert my landing page into the
text that I want to put into some kind
of a video ad like that. Okay. Now,
again, remember I mentioned competitor
analysis. So, I would look at like what
is the visual that you might want to
generate or represent. So what I did was
I asked it,
okay, describe a visual of a beach
setting that would fit the background of
this ad for that text. Include a pink
flamingo floaty computer and a hat on
the ground in the beach. So again, this
is like an idea that I had for the beach
ad. And then I'm gonna have the AI
generate me what the scene is going to
look like. Okay, so it's generating me
the scene. Here's the beach setting.
Imagine a pristine. Okay, generate me a
prompt for one a video
a photo
generation AI that can take text to
image to make this
scene. into an image to video generation
AI, a prompt to take the generated image
to turn it into a motion scene that is
five seconds long. Okay. And we can do
all this inside of chat GPT now, which
is amazing because we have access to
Sora and we have access to there's other
video AIs out there like Clling and VO
from Google. Uh but right here, look at
it was able to generate prompts for us
right here. create a a beach scene right
there. Turquoise ocean da da. And it's
going to turn this into this kind of a
video right there. Okay. So, what I'm
going to do now is I'm going to go over
to
Sora,
sora.com, and we're going to generate
everything right inside of
Sora.
Okay, that's what we're going to do.
Okay, so here's Sora. Look, you can
explore different things. So we have
these are images that were generated
with Sora. You can generate both images
and videos. That's the beauty of
Sora. These are all AI generated
videos that Sora created. Amazing.
Okay. So I'm going to go to uh this and
I'm going to show you. We can prompt it
for an image. You can tell it to make it
2x3 stand up make two images. We're
going to paste the image right there.
Then we're going to tell it to generate
those images for me. Okay. And it's
amazing how it's able to actually do
that. Now I'm going to show you just for
an example how we did this earlier. We
told it to generate these images right
there. But then we also prompted the
visual landscape to create the cinematic
right there as well.
So, same thing. You can copy this in
and try telling it to make that into
like a
video right
there. Only generate one video or image
at a time. So, yes, that's one of the
limitations with this is you're only
able to generate one at a time. But just
for the sake of the example, that's
exactly how we prompted these as well.
That's how we were able to generate
these images right here in these videos
by using the
prompts. I told it to remix it and zoom
the camera in a bit to show the
beach. Uh this was one a little bit of a
different angle. The glasses disappear,
which is funny, but like the reflection
on the beach and all that just
beautiful. It's amazing. Like it's it's
perfectly good enough to be able to use
for an ad all day long. The visuals are
incredible. This one was a little much.
Like I didn't want to wash up the beach
right there. Right. That's that's kind
of makes me nervous. But this one's
beautiful. Just amazing shot right
there. Like I want to be there,
right? And so that's exactly what we
were we were able to do. And so again,
using chat GPT, using tools like Sora,
uh it's it's amazing.
I would not try to generate scenes like
this on my own necessarily. I would ask
chat GPT to give me the prompt to use
because it knows how to prompt Sora to
make beautiful videos. Not all the
videos are going to be great. So like
here's here's the two that it generated
right here. We could copy that image. We
could use that as
a
reference. And then we could tell it to
create the video.
So, let's make a video. So, there's our
our reference clips right there. It's
funny. They're not much different from
each other, but this one's definitely
much
better. Interesting choice of photo on
the screen, too. Okay. So, then Sora is
going to go then go to work to make us
the video that's gonna based on that.
And you can test it out where you either
use a video with inspiration
uh or you don't. I made some kind of
crazy stuff inside of Sora. I was making
one right here with like a like a guy in
it, you know? He's like stepping on a
It's weird. It kind of It It's kind of
weird when you use people in the app,
but for like I animated my son's toys
and stuff like that. I made some clips
of me right here in the Revolutionary
War. This is just some some fun stuff I
was playing around with as well.
There's a clip of me on a
dinosaur. There's another clip of me on
a dinosaur. These are all just crazy fun
stuff I was making here with Sora. So,
yep. Very cool how we're able to do
that. And so then what I would do is I
would take those
videos and I would go into Google Drive.
Okay? So I could download the video
file, go into Google Drive, and then I
can save it over to my phone. And then
by saving it over to my phone, I can
open it up in
Instagram. So what I was able to do is I
was able to literally open it up in
Instagram, open up the video file that I
saved and tell it, all right, let's make
let's make an Instagram reel with like
this video right here.
Okay, let's make an Instagram real with
that video. literally can go right into
Instagram, add our text to it.
POV Hello. See, you can add any text
over to Instagram right
there. And it's it's amazing being able
to do this. I was able to then even
generate multiple. I could replace the
video simply by selecting the video,
swapping out the video, and I made
multiple versions of the same ad by
doing that. So, my workflow is I go like
from some video clip into Instagram to
add the text and then I download it from
Instagram
um to be able to run it. One last thing
that I'll do is I'll use AI as well to
maybe generate me some royalty-free
music or I'll download some. So, there's
an app. It's called
sununo.com. Using sununo.com is really
great for generating music and the
quality of the music is really really
cool for ads.
So like if I wanted to generate this
right
here, I might use
suno, I might say
uh quality. Okay, I want a beachy
vibe something like
surfer tune chill. We're going to do it
instrumental. Then we can tell it to
create
that. And now Sunno is gonna go to work
creating some kind of like a like a
instrumental beachy vibe surf rock
type type
[Music]
thing. That's
cool. I was having fun with
different
styles. It's a fun
app generating for like generating music
and stuff. Uh here Sora went to work and
it kind of created us some of our little
video clips right
here. So sometimes it does good for
that, sometimes it doesn't. This one it
it was not as good. So what I might do
is just generate it just
simply. What I like to do is I like to
generate an image to kind of preview the
angle of it and then adjust it from
there. We can just generate the the
video by itself and use that. Sorry, I
know I'm bouncing around a lot here, but
that's the process that I would use very
simply. I can use an app like InShot to
add the video uh the audio, the music
onto the video. And now I can run that
as a as a Facebook ad. I can bring it
into Google Drive, bring it over into
the Facebook ads manager, and now I have
these beautiful videos and things like
that that I can use. Listen, if you're
trying to have unique ads on Instagram,
things like that, you could literally
come up with like limitless styles of
ads, videos, things like that using
these types of tools like this. Okay?
So, plug in, try them out, and listen,
if you're a coach, mentor, or trainer,
and you'd love to work with me to be
able to help you get more clients in
your business and no longer struggle,
but actually create the kind of wealth
that's possible for you. My Wealthy
Coach Academy program is something that
I work with people every single week to
build their businesses together. They I
get to come alongside them and show them
exactly how to do that. You can click
the link in the description below and
I'll walk you through step by step the
best way to get started working with me
on that. We'll talk soon everybody.